andybeard.eu 2013-12-01

# Privacy Statement

Please don’t interact with this website if you are under 13 – I have no wish to have any of your personal data.

If you leave a comment your email address will be stored in my database on my server. Please refer to my comments policy about how I reserve the right to contact you if you leave a comment for a number of reasons, at my own discretion.

I use various forms of tracking, and some of these services don’t identify personal data, and others might to a greater or lesser extent. I will almost always know general details like what IP address you have, browser, screen resolution, where you came from, and what pages you read.

At certain times I may also know what actions you took on my site, such as which links were clicked, and with services like MyBlogLog, I may even be able to identify data down to individual people.

Subscriptions by RSS are effectively anonymous. For email subscriptions the service is provided by Feedburner, and isn’t anonymous, as I get to see email addresses.

I try to keep all data secure, and where possible I will delete it upon request.

Please also refer to the [MyBlogLog privacy policy](http://www.mybloglog.com/buzz/privacy/)

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads all over the internet, and maybe on this site on occasion.

Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visits to this site and other sites on the Internet.

Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

“This site uses SeeVolution web analytics service. SeeVolution may record mouse clicks, mouse movements, scrolling activity as well as any text you type in this website. SeeVolution does not collect personally identifiable information that you do not voluntarily enter in this website. SeeVolution does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use SeeVolution services. For more information visit: http://SeeVolution.com/privacypolicy. You can choose to disable the Service at http://www.seevolution.net/disable.html.”
